IZABEL LIMA

BRAZILIAN WEB DEVELOPER

+55 11 98133.0385 b.lima.izabel@gmail.com izabellima.com A highly creative professional with ten years experience in the visual communication field who decided to pursue the long-held interest in programming. Resourceful and determined, has been able to apply previously acquired skills to problem-solving, thinking both visually and analytically. Looking for an opportunity to delve deeply into the web development world, face new challenges, expand skills and grow as a professional.

Work experience

FREELANCE DESIGNER (SEPTEMBER 2015 - PRESENT)

Provided design work for the following clients:

- Salami Social Club (DE) Logo, posters, flyers and Facebook posts
- Dermiwil (BR) Designed the company's annual product brochure
- Yello Media (BR) Logo and banner design for Yello Media's clients (Marcella Tranchesi, Bru Real Life, WePick, Giordana Serrano, Nadia Tambasco)
- · Bicyclette London Repair (UK) Logo design
- FHITS (BR) Corporate presentation for the biggest platform of digital influencers in South America.
- BC Comunicação (BR) Menu and Menu Board design for Häagen-Dazs Brazi's RFP pitch.

ART DIRECTOR AT AIDIA (APRIL 2014 - AUGUST 2015)

Babies Annual. Brides Annual).

Designed a vast array of artwork for clients such as Mapfre, Tetra Pak, Petz, Roadcard, Styrolution and Solvey.

DESIGNER AT EDITORA CARAS (APRIL 2007 - NOVEMBER 2013)

Visual communication artwork for the publisher's marketing department (ads, posters, flyers, invitations, uniforms, trophies, banners, websites); Editorial layout and photo production for segmented magazines (Fashion Bi-annual, Interior Design Annual

EDUCATION

ESPM - SP (2005-2008)

Bachelor's Degree in Design (Visual Design with emphasis in Marketing)

LE WAGON - BERLIN (2017 | BATCH#65)

FullStack 9-week intensive Bootcamp

TECH SKILLS

Ruby on Rails Git
HTML GitHub
CSS Heroku
Bootstrap

JavaScript Ir jQuery Il PostgreSQL

Indesign Photoshop Illustrator

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Portuguese Native
English Fluent
German A1